Welcome to the end of this section on introducing the project management components I told you it was
a big section.
A lot of information here to talk about.
You looked at the Project Management components the process groups and the knowledge areas.
That alone is really big.
And then you've had an opportunity to map out the processes the 14:9 processes.
So you were starting to learn about where processors are exist in the process groups and the knowledge
areas.
Of course the Pinback guide and this course is structured on knowledge areas.
Your exam is cross-reference with the process groups the initiating planning executing monitor and controlling
and closing.
So we talked about those how they relate to each other.
We looked at work performance data information and reports we're going to see those a lot throughout
the course we'll see data as an input and sometimes information and then we'll see reports as an output
occasionally as an input something to watch for.
We've talked about tailoring the processes adaptive environments.
The business case in our first official planned the project benefit management plan.
So how will you manage the benefits that the project bring to the organization.
Okay a lot of information that you've covered.
Good job you are making great progress.
We have a lot of information to cover but look at how far you've come in your effort already as you
prepare to pass the PMP.
Okay I want you to keep moving on.
I'll see you in the next section.